Hello, everyone. I'm Momokin, also known
as Sakurai Momo from NOT EQUAL ME.
Today, I'm going to a karaoke by myself.
Yeah!
And I heard that I'll get a reward
depending on the player who comes out.
I don't like to lose, so I'll do my best
to get a high score.
I'm going to sing 10 songs.
What should I sing first?
I think a song that makes you feel like
you're opening your throat is good.
Here it is.
It's Gotama's Gotama's.
I sing this song a lot, so I think I can
sing it well.
I'm going to sing this song a lot, so I
think I can sing it well.
I'm sorry for running to your dry heart
I'm sorry for not being able to do
anything
You won't forgive me
I turned around to live
I turned my back and left, lonely love
I'll be with you, no matter what
Even in the darkness of the world
You are shining
Beyond the future
So that my soul won't be destroyed by
weakness
My way
I'll overlap now
Our prayers
Don't forget
Like the hot night
I'm lost in the reality
I want to see you, but I don't have a
reason to feel good
You are the reason for my overflowing
love
Even if it's just a beautiful dream
I'll chase you while drawing a picture
for you, love me now
Stop it, you're not the one to lie
Look ahead, I'm prepared for what's to
come
Even in the dark future, I'll become
stronger
I can change my fate, my wish
Even though I want to make it come true,
everything is a loss
You were here, I was here
And the others have disappeared
While drawing the beauty of a faint
dream
I trace the scars
That's why I'm following you
No matter what kind of world, even in
the darkness
I'm sure you will
Shine and overcome the future
So that the soul won't be destroyed by
weakness
Now, now, let's overlap
The two of us, let's
The first song is over.
I'm excited.
How is it?
The first song is 97 points.
Then, I should do the next one.
I should do the next one.
I'm going to be sick for a month.
The second song is No Thank You by
POKUROTI TIME.
No Thank You by POKUROTI TIME
I don't need to be cured
Because I love you so much
I want to be a mature girl
I want to be a little girl again
My heart is pounding
I want to be a mature girl again
97.13%
Well, it's only the second song.
I'm not sure if I can sing it well.
I'll sing more and more songs.
The second song is...
I'm going to sing Ikuwa Mio's song,
Kono Sora ga Trigger.
It was 98 points.
I'll sing it with my best.
When I look up at the dazzling sun,
I want to see you.
This sky is a trigger.
I knew from the beginning that I had a
lover
A story-like love, just a friend
The day the blue sky was beautiful
I haven't forgotten that day
Everything I see
This is the song that reminds me of you
My youth
That sky was a story
The sky that you like
The wind that blows towards you
deceives love in a vague way
I know I shouldn't tell you this feeling
But, but, but, but
You are always in my heart
I remember the day when the sky was
beautiful
You think of someone
But you say you like me without
permission
I don't care about this
I only know the sky
This love
Keep it a secret
I want to remember the things we did
that day
I got 96 points for this song.
I see.
I'll add some lyrics to this song.
I'll sing Aiko's song, KISS HUG.
KISS HUG by Aiko
From the day I met you
Now, now
Summer is coming
I'm sure I'll remember it when I get
older
Your shadow
My words
Our face in the mirror
Suddenly, I touched your lips
I swear I'll be by your side
Your love, your love, goodbye
You love, you love, you love
Army God
I think I sang it really well, but I'm
not sure if I can do it.
She is still not sure.
I have to sing my favorite song.
I've been practicing this song since I
was in kindergarten.
It's Mika Nakashima's song, Orion.
I've been singing this song for a long
time.
I think I can sing this song.
Thank you.
So sweet...
I was the one who cried
That's why I can't show my weakness
I wanted to tell you that I'm not strong
I believe
Thank you for watching!
I'm out of breath, on my way home, the
stars are melting
I'm about to forget even the faint
warmth of the past
I realized for the first time that I can
love someone
I was the one who cried
The constellations of winter that
connected
I was staring at them as if they were
disappearing into the sky
Only for you
It was me
Showing weakness, that's how it is
It's because those days ain't locked
away
With those strong reasons
I believe
I said it, so I believe
【 lashes went very up with going up at
once】
【 the magic went back on the lamp to
relax the state of the room again】
I did it !
【IIII that feel so good! I did it !】
I'm so glad!
I got 20,000 yen!
I did it!
I will sing a song of my favorite
singer, and I will enjoy singing it!
【Mahoroba Starisco】
My heart is beating fast, I've made a
star
I want to be a star that doesn't get
lonely
But still, but still, every time I meet
you
I shine the night with my bright
strength
I'm just staring at you, that's all I
need
But still, my feelings rush towards the
fall
That's right, this love is a magical
birthday disk
A small, tiny copy of the palm of my
hand
Is written on this notebook
I can feel your smile
It's fine if it doesn't reach you
The shooting stars are moving you
Beyond the galaxy
Always alone
I said I love you, no matter how many
times I call you
I can't even say it, I'm so weak
Your happiness is somewhere near
It's not me, it's someone else's bright
path
Maybe, yes, I understand
You're the starry sky
It's so bright, I'm going to be out of
focus
I'm sure we'll meet again
The stars between you and me are each
twinkling
Tomorrow, I'll surely be talking to you
I'll be thinking about you all night
Translated by Releska
Let me cherish you just for now
I love that girl, I love you
I think we're mixed in the stardust
I sang all the songs!
I remember singing alone in private.
I was very nervous because I was
planning to sing alone on this channel.
But, I enjoyed singing!
The highest score is 98!
I'll challenge again!
That's all!
I'm Momoki.
I'm Sakurai Momo.
Bye bye!